{"message": "", "questions": [{"answer": 3, "question": "How many sentences are there in this paragraph?", "question_type": 1}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Cardinal number.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["survived", "The", "of", "20"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Pural Noun.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["only", "Kyrgyzstan", "people", "of"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (non 3rd person singular present tense).", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["have", "civil", "passengers", "The"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past participle).", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["survived", "about", "that", "of"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["passengers", "'s", "head", "The"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["only", "and", "that", "The"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Pural singular Noun.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["authority", "Kyrgyzstan", "The", "civil"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["The", "of", "head", "Kyrgyzstan"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["have", "civil", "about", "of"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Possessive ending.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["authority", "'s", "of", "90"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["20", "that", "about", "authority"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["aviation", "about", "20", "survived"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["people", "only", "have", "that"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["aviation", "that", "about", "said"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["crew", "90", "of", "The"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["Kyrgyzstan", "out", "20", "have"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Cardinal number.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["90", "crew", "have", "said"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["head", "about", "Kyrgyzstan", "survived"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Coordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["and", "civil", "that", "aviation"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Pural Noun.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["Kyrgyzstan", "out", "passengers", "crew"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["only", "crew", "and", "The"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["about", "authority", "'s", "only"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["have", "only", "90", "of"]}, {"explanation": "20 is Cardinal number", "question": "Is 20, Cardinal number in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "people is Pural Noun", "question": "Is people, Pural Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "have is Verb (non 3rd person singular present tense)", "question": "Is have, Verb (non 3rd person singular present tense) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "survived is Verb (past participle)", "question": "Is survived, Superlative Adverb in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "head is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is head, Verb (past participle) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "The is Determiner", "question": "Is The, Superlative Adjective in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Kyrgyzstan is Pural singular Noun", "question": "Is Kyrgyzstan, WH-pronoun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "of is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is of, Preposition or subordinating conjunction in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "civil is Adjective", "question": "Is civil, Singular or mass Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "'s is Possessive ending", "question": "Is 's, Symbol in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "authority is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is authority, Interjection in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "aviation is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is aviation, Superlative Adverb in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "that is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is that, Interjection in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "said is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Is said, Verb (past tense) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "of is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is of, Foreign word in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "out is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is out, WH-determiner in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "90 is Cardinal number", "question": "Is 90, Cardinal number in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "about is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is about, Foreign word in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "and is Coordinating conjunction", "question": "Is and, Verb (3rd person singular present tense) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "passengers is Pural Noun", "question": "Is passengers, Pural singular Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "crew is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is crew, List item marker in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "about is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is about, Predeterminer in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "only is Adverb", "question": "Is only, Adverb in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "20 is Cardinal number", "question": "Select appropiate Cardinal number from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about _____________ people have survived .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["10", "737", "90", "20"]}, {"explanation": "head is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The _____________ of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["head", "number", "name", "authority"]}, {"explanation": "The is Determiner", "question": "Select appropiate Determiner from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": " _____________ head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["some", "The", "a", "those"]}, {"explanation": "Kyrgyzstan is Pural singular Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Pural singular Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The head of _____________ 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["Mashhad", "Kyrgyzstan", "Iran", "Air"]}, {"explanation": "of is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The head _____________ Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["from", "on", "out", "of"]}, {"explanation": "authority is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation _____________ said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["manan", "board", "khushboo", "authority"]}, {"explanation": "aviation is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil _____________ authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["plane", "capital", "aviation", "crew"]}, {"explanation": "that is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said _____________ out of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["for", "that", "in", "of"]}, {"explanation": "of is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out _____________ about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["of", "after", "from", "in"]}, {"explanation": "out is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that _____________ of about 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["for", "on", "about", "out"]}, {"explanation": "90 is Cardinal number", "question": "Select appropiate Cardinal number from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about _____________ passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["20", "90", "737", "10"]}, {"explanation": "about is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of _____________ 90 passengers and crew , only about 20 people have survived .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["out", "that", "about", "after"]}, {"explanation": "crew is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and _____________ , only about 20 people have survived .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["crew", "take-off", "round", "number"]}, {"explanation": "about is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The head of Kyrgyzstan 's civil aviation authority said that out of about 90 passengers and crew , only _____________ 20 people have survived .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["for", "out", "about", "in"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["those", "a", "passenger", "of"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["Ram", "plane", "those", "capital"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["on", "shortly", "Bishkek", "board"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["board", "Bishkek", "Dr.", "of"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Pural singular Noun.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["a", "plane", "capital", "Ram"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Pural singular Noun.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["a", "has", "Dr.", "take-off"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["large", "has", "after", "plane"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["crashed", "passenger", "of", "those"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past participle).", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["Ram", "has", "after", "crashed"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (3rd person singular present tense).", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["Bishkek", "has", "a", "those"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["Kyrgyzstan", "after", "a", "crashed"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["from", "Bishkek", "Kyrgyzstan", "shortly"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["passenger", "from", "capital", "Dr."]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["from", "take-off", "large", "has"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Possessive ending.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["take-off", "Bishkek", "'s", "on"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Pural singular Noun.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["those", "number", "has", "Kyrgyzstan"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["Ram", "Kyrgyzstan", "capital", "from"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Pural singular Noun.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["plane", "Bishkek", "of", "shortly"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["has", "a", "after", "Ram"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (present participle).", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["number", "large", "Ram", "killing"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["has", "number", "Kyrgyzstan", "a"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["take-off", "'s", "large", "killing"]}, {"explanation": "of is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is of, Cardinal number in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "those is Determiner", "question": "Is those, Determiner in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "on is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is on, Pural singular Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "board is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is board, Singular or mass Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Ram is Pural singular Noun", "question": "Is Ram, Pural singular Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Dr. is Pural singular Noun", "question": "Is Dr., Pural singular Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "plane is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is plane, Singular or mass Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "passenger is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is passenger, Verb (3rd person singular present tense) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "crashed is Verb (past participle)", "question": "Is crashed, Verb (past participle) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "has is Verb (3rd person singular present tense)", "question": "Is has, Verb (3rd person singular present tense) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "after is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is after, Preposition or subordinating conjunction in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "shortly is Adverb", "question": "Is shortly, WH-determiner in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "from is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is from, Preposition or subordinating conjunction in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "take-off is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is take-off, Singular or mass Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "'s is Possessive ending", "question": "Is 's, Verb (non 3rd person singular present tense) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Kyrgyzstan is Pural singular Noun", "question": "Is Kyrgyzstan, Wh-adverb in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "capital is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is capital, Singular or mass Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Bishkek is Pural singular Noun", "question": "Is Bishkek, Possessive WH-pronoun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "a is Determiner", "question": "Is a, Determiner in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "killing is Verb (present participle)", "question": "Is killing, WH-pronoun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "number is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is number, Preposition or subordinating conjunction in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "large is Adjective", "question": "Is large, Foreign word in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "of is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number _____________ those on board .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["after", "from", "that", "of"]}, {"explanation": "those is Determiner", "question": "Select appropiate Determiner from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of _____________ on board .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["those", "The", "some", "a"]}, {"explanation": "on is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those _____________ board .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["from", "on", "after", "out"]}, {"explanation": "board is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on _____________ .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["board", "passenger", "capital", "number"]}, {"explanation": "Ram is Pural singular Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Pural singular Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Dr. _____________ passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["Iran", "Bishkek", "Ram", "Air"]}, {"explanation": "Dr. is Pural singular Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Pural singular Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": " _____________ Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["Mashhad", "Kyrgyzstan", "Dr.", "Itek"]}, {"explanation": "plane is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger _____________ has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["capital", "authority", "passenger", "plane"]}, {"explanation": "passenger is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram _____________ plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["passenger", "authority", "round", "aviation"]}, {"explanation": "after is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly _____________ take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["for", "after", "of", "from"]}, {"explanation": "from is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off _____________ Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["of", "about", "out", "from"]}, {"explanation": "take-off is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after _____________ from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["take-off", "number", "capital", "manan"]}, {"explanation": "Kyrgyzstan is Pural singular Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Pural singular Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from _____________ 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["Bishkek", "Mashhad", "Kyrgyzstan", "Itek"]}, {"explanation": "capital is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's _____________ , Bishkek , killing a large number of those on board .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["authority", "capital", "manan", "head"]}, {"explanation": "Bishkek is Pural singular Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Pural singular Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , _____________ , killing a large number of those on board .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["Mashhad", "Boeing", "Bishkek", "Kyrgyzstan"]}, {"explanation": "a is Determiner", "question": "Select appropiate Determiner from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing _____________ large number of those on board .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["those", "some", "The", "a"]}, {"explanation": "number is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Dr. Ram passenger plane has crashed shortly after take-off from Kyrgyzstan 's capital , Bishkek , killing a large _____________ of those on board .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["number", "aviation", "crew", "round"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Pural Noun.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["Itek", "minutes", "later", "some"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["bound", "later", "Itek", "737"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Pural singular Noun.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["for", "turned", "Itek", "10"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["Mashhad", "but", "737", "The"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Pural singular Noun.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["Boeing", "The", "some", "off"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Pural singular Noun.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["turned", "north-eastern", "Air", "bound"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["737", "The", "took", "Air"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Cardinal number.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["Itek", "737", "Boeing", "in"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past participle).", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["bound", "off", "but", "later"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Particle.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["for", "some", "bound", "off"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Pural singular Noun.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["for", "in", "took", "Mashhad"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["north-eastern", "10", "Air", "for"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["round", "in", "The", "Iran"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Pural singular Noun.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["minutes", "in", "Iran", "off"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["The", "Boeing", "Air", "north-eastern"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Coordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["minutes", "10", "but", "737"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["some", "took", "round", "bound"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["minutes", "turned", "Iran", "Boeing"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Cardinal number.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["10", "minutes", "turned", "in"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["Mashhad", "some", "bound", "10"]}, {"explanation": "minutes is Pural Noun", "question": "Is minutes, Pural Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "later is Adverb", "question": "Is later, Singular or mass Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Itek is Pural singular Noun", "question": "Is Itek, Pural singular Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "The is Determiner", "question": "Is The, Determiner in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Boeing is Pural singular Noun", "question": "Is Boeing, Comparative Adverb in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Air is Pural singular Noun", "question": "Is Air, Pural singular Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "took is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Is took, Verb (past tense) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "737 is Cardinal number", "question": "Is 737, Possessive pronoun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "bound is Verb (past participle)", "question": "Is bound, Personal pronoun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "off is Particle", "question": "Is off, Verb (base form) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Mashhad is Pural singular Noun", "question": "Is Mashhad, Possessive ending in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "for is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is for, Verb (present participle) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "in is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is in, Possessive pronoun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Iran is Pural singular Noun", "question": "Is Iran, Pural singular Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "north-eastern is Adjective", "question": "Is north-eastern, Adjective in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "but is Coordinating conjunction", "question": "Is but, Verb (3rd person singular present tense) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "round is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is round, Symbol in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "turned is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Is turned, Verb (past tense) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "10 is Cardinal number", "question": "Is 10, Cardinal number in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "some is Determiner", "question": "Is some, Determiner in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Itek is Pural singular Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Pural singular Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The _____________ Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["Itek", "Kyrgyzstan", "Mashhad", "Dr."]}, {"explanation": "The is Determiner", "question": "Select appropiate Determiner from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": " _____________ Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["some", "those", "The", "a"]}, {"explanation": "Boeing is Pural singular Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Pural singular Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air _____________ 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["Boeing", "Kyrgyzstan", "Ram", "Itek"]}, {"explanation": "Air is Pural singular Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Pural singular Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The Itek _____________ Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["Itek", "Dr.", "Air", "Bishkek"]}, {"explanation": "737 is Cardinal number", "question": "Select appropiate Cardinal number from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing _____________ took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["20", "90", "10", "737"]}, {"explanation": "Mashhad is Pural singular Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Pural singular Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for _____________ , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["Boeing", "Ram", "Itek", "Mashhad"]}, {"explanation": "for is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound _____________ Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["out", "for", "of", "about"]}, {"explanation": "in is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , _____________ north-eastern Iran , but turned round some 10 minutes later .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["in", "of", "about", "out"]}, {"explanation": "Iran is Pural singular Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Pural singular Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern _____________ , but turned round some 10 minutes later .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["Ram", "Bishkek", "Iran", "Dr."]}, {"explanation": "round is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned _____________ some 10 minutes later .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["plane", "number", "round", "manan"]}, {"explanation": "10 is Cardinal number", "question": "Select appropiate Cardinal number from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round some _____________ minutes later .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["10", "737", "20", "90"]}, {"explanation": "some is Determiner", "question": "Select appropiate Determiner from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The Itek Air Boeing 737 took off bound for Mashhad , in north-eastern Iran , but turned round _____________ 10 minutes later .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["some", "The", "those", "a"]}], "success": 1}